Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series VI. White House Correspondence
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - Q, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - R, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - S, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - T, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - U, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - V, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - W, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - X, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - Y, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - Z, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - White House Files (1), 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - White House Files (2), 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - A, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - B, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Airlines, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Alumnae, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - deButts, John, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Biographies - Mr. Kahn & Pictures, 1978 - 80 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - C, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - D, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - E, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - F, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - G, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - H, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - I, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - J, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - K, 1978 - 80 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - L, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - M, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - N, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - O, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - P, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Personal, 1978 - 80 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Q, 1978 - 80 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - R, 1978 - 80 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - S, 1978 - 80 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Stelzer, Irwin, 1978 - 80 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Style Memo, 1978 - 80 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - T, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - U, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - V, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - W, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Z, 1978 - 80 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Series VII. White House Dissertation
  - Book Draft with Notes: The Position of Great Britain in the World Economy, 1942 - 44 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, No Date (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - A Photo of Kahn, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Certificates Kahn Received, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Album: Kahn with White House, 1978 - 80 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Photography Collection of Kahn's, 1979 - 80 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. White House
  - Report and Publications, 1979 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda, 1979 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 1, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence "M", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence "N", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence "O", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence "P", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence "Q", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence "R", 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Files Related to Administrative Conference of the United States, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Rm 208 1/9/79, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Meeting 4:30PM - Dec. 28, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Dec. 14, 1978, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Inflation, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Health Anti-Inlfation Task Force (2 Notebooks), 1978 - 79 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Alternative Gas Tax And Recycling Proposals, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Appointment Books (5 Notebooks), 1978 - 80 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Series IX. Speeches
  - Economic Issues in Regulating the Field Price of Nat. Gas - May, 1960, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - American Econimc Review - June, 1964, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - The Tyranny of Small Decisions: Market Failures, Imperfections, & the Limitis of Economics, AEK (KYKLOS, VOL. XIX), 1966 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Resource Journal - Jan., 1970, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "Economics of Electronicity Environmental Issue, A Primer" - June, 1972, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Market Power Inflation: A Conceptual Framework - Cornell Univ. - Apr., 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Fortune Magazine Letter to the Editor - Apr., 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - "Economic Theory as Guideline for Gov't Intervention & Control" - June, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Jackson Committee Hearings - Aug. 8, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Senate Committee on Interior & Insular Affiars - Washington, DC - Aug. 8, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Wall St. Utility Group New York City - Sept. 17, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Russell Sage College Lecture Troy, New York - Sept. 30, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Alumni Associatioin Cornell Club - New York City - Oct. 16, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Association of Edison Illuminating Companies Greenbrier - Oct. 25, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Press Conference New York City - Nov. 25, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Seminar - University of Tenn. Knoxville, Tenn. - Dec. 4, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Energy Resources Council Project Independence Washington DC - Dec. 11, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - TALK of New York State Public Service Commission - Dec. 18, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - New York Society of Security Analysts New York City - Dec. 18, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - American Economic Association San Francisco, Cali. - Dec. 28-30, 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Practice and Procedures - Feb. 6, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Efficient Rate Design - The Transition from Theory to Practice - Feb. 24, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Presentation of Paper at University of Missouri, Crown Center, Kansas City, Missouri - Feb. 24-26, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Sen. Muskie Committee Washington, DC - Mar. 7, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Committes on Corp., Authoroties and Commission - Assembly Parlor - Albany, NY - Mar. 17, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Senate Commerce Subcommittee Dirksen Senate Office Bldg. Washington, DC - Mar. 17, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Balancing the Energy Future of New York State - Mar. 21, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - West Side Conference for 29th Senatorial Dist. - Columbia Univ. New York City - Apr. 19, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Tapings and Interviews - New York City - May 1-2, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Speech - "Inflation" Harmanus Bleeker Library Albany, NY - May 6, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - The Recognition of Environmental Costs - May 20, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - New York State Utilities Exec. Conference, Lake Placid, NY - Sept. 22, 1974, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - NY Society of Security Analysts' Seminar on Impact of Energy Shortage on US Economy NYC - Jan. 9, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Gabrielson Lectures on Public Policy-Colby College, Waterville, Maine - Feb. 20, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Conf. on "Energy and Government: Towards A Sounds Oil Policy - Sen. Haskell Washington, DC - Mar. 20, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Syracuse Press Club Syracuse, NY - Mar. 21, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Legislative & Political Conf. Communications Workers of America Camelot Restaurant - Mar. 25, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Microeconomic Workshop, Yale University New Haven, Conn. - Apr. 3, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Executive Development Program University of Rochester Rochester, NY - Apr. 11, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Baruch College NYC - Apr. 17, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - RPI Economics Dept. Seminar Troy, NY - May 14, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - National Energy Forum III Washington, DC - May 15-16, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Iowa State University Regulatory Conference - May 20, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Edison Electric Institute Annual Convention Denver, Colo. - June 3, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Electricity Costs, Pricing and Use A Regulatory Evaluation - June 3, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - New York State Telephone Assoc. Inc., - Great Gorge, NJ - June 8-10, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Evening Lectures Ithaca, NY - July 16, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Meeting with Peter Rodino House Judiciary Committee Washington, DC - June 19, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Statement before Sen. Committee on Finance (Sen. Haskell) Washington, DC - July 18, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Energy Conservation and Conversation Act of 1975 - July 18, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Between Theory and Practice: Reflections of a Neophyte Public Utility Regulator, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Onondaga County Citizens Committee for Energy Conservation Syracuse,NY - July 25, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Productivity Seminar - Aug. 11-12, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - NYS Utilities Executive Conference Cooperstown, NY - Sept. 22, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Kremer Assem. Comm. On Corps., Authorities & Commissions NYC - Sept. 24, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Lifeline Electric Rates - Sept. 24, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University - Carleton University Conference on North American Energy Policy Ottawa, CAN. - Oct. 2-4, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Implications of An Electrification Strategy For Canada and the United States - Oct. 3, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Fuel and Gas Adjustment Cl. Sen. Committee Buffalo, NY - Oct. 22, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Sen. McFarland's Committee on Fuel Adjustment Clause Buffalo, NY - Oct. 22, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - University of Boston School of Law - Boston, Mass. - Oct. 23, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - SUNY, Exec. Breakfast SUNY Campus Albany, NY - Oct. 24, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - NARUC Meeting Boston, Mass. - Nov. 3-6, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Hse Sbcmte on Communications re Domestic Comm Carrier Regulation - Nov. 18, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Testimony before House Sub-Committee on Communications Washington, DC - Nov. 18, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Joint Economic Committee Seminar "The Economics of Commission Regulation" - Library of Congress Washington, DC - Nov. 24, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Torch Club - Albany, New York - Dec. 1, 1975, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - New Rate Structures in Communications/Fortnightly Washington, DC, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Women's Club Schenectady, NY - Jan. 14, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - NYC Smith Barney Eelectric Utility Conference - Jan. 15, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Smith-Barney Electric Util. Conf. New York City - Jan. 15, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - PURC Conference Gainesville, Florida - Feb. 3-4, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - WHEN TV Studio Syracuse, NY- Feb. 12, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Aspen Institute Seminar on Communications Technologies Brookings Institution Washington, DC - Feb. 19, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Technical Education Conference Washington, DC - Feb. 19-20, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - University of Rochester - Apr. 2, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Hse Cmte on Interstate & Foreign Com. Sbcmte on Energy & Power-H.R.12461 - Apr. 7, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Testimony before House Committee on Interstate & Foreign Commerce Dingell/Moss Bill Washington, DC - Apr. 7, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Convocation New York City - Apr. 10, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Mayor Beame's Conference on Consumerism - New York City - Apr. 27, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Trends in Utility Costs Past and Future - New York City - Apr. 27, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - The Regulator's Role in Maintaining Reliable Elec. Service Hartford, Conn. - Apr. 29, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Northeast Power Coordinating Council Seminar Hartford, Conn. - Apr. 29, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Milton Miscus Seminar Albany, NY - May 3, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - EPRI Seminar Series "Perspectives on Elec. Util. Industry" Palo Alto, Calif. - May 27, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Challenge Magazine Article - June, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Fund Tower Club - Charter Society Dinner Albany, NY - June 2, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - 54th National Conf on Reg. Utility Comm. Engineers Hershey, PA re Economics… - June 23, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - National Conference of Regulatory Utility Commission Engineers Hershey, PA - June 23, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Law School Lilly Lecture Ithaca, NY - July 12, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Testimony in Case 26806 Albany, NY July 14-16, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - EPRI Seminar San Diego, CA - July 26, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - EPRI Journal Interview San Francisco, CA - July 28, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - EEI Chief Executives Meeting on R&D - Denver, Colorado - Aug. 13, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - NARUC Annual Regulatory Studies Program - Michigan State Univ. E. Lansing, Mich - Aug. 26, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Conference on "Natural Gas in the Northeast" Providence, R.I. - Spet. 9, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - American Economic Association Atlantic City, N.J. - Sept. 16-17, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Amer. Economics Assoc., Atlantic City, JN, Utility Rate Reg.: Appl of Econ. - Spet. 17, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - House Cmte on Interstate & Foreign Commerce re Consumer Com. Reform Act… - Sept. 30, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Testimony before the House Subcommittee on Communications Washington, DC - Sept. 30, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Governor and State Commisioners Meeting with Young Company Presidents Albany NY - Oct. 7, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Public Utility Law of the State Bar Association New York City - Oct. 14, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Consumer Assembly Conference New York City - Oct. 30, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - NERA-Kidder, Peabody Seminar Litchfield Park, Arizona - Nov. 3, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - 87th Annual Conv. Of NARUC re New Rate Structures in Comm. Boston, Mass. - Nov. 3-6, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Heights College Annual Awards Dinner - New York City - Nov. 10, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - St. Lawrence Energy Council Postdam, NY - Nov. 11, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Panel Dis., Hawaii, 88th Annual Conv. NARUC - Nov. 15-18, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Meeting of National Association of Regulatory Utility Commrs., Honolulu, Hawaii - Nov. 15-19, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - WHEN-TV 10 Taping "Pulse" Program Albany, NY - Nov. 29, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - ABA Symposium on Ratemaking Washington, DC - Dec. 9, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Conf. on Dengell Util. Rate Reform Bill, Public Interest Economics Foundation Washington, DC - Dec. 9, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - WMCA Taping (Elinor Guggenheimer) New York City - Dec. 10, 1976, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - FBA Communications Law Workshop Washington, DC - Jan. 31, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - RFF National Energy Strategies Forum Washington, DC - Feb. 4, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of Society of Gas Lighting Engineers New York City - Feb. 10, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rate Design Symposium Kansas City, Missouri - Feb. 15, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Sen McFarland Committee Testimony on Natural Gas Albany, NY - Feb.16, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Third Annual Symp. on Problems of Regulated Industries Kansas City, Missouri - Feb. 14, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Sen. Cmte on Corp., Auth. & Public Utilities NY State - Feb. 16, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - US Sen Cmte on Commerce re The Communications Act of 1934, Revisited - Mar. 21, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Old Speech Files, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Testimony before US Sen. Hollings Committee on Bell Bill Washington, DC - Mar. 21, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Stewart Myers Seminar - Cost of Capital Albany NY - Mar. 30, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Fifth Annual Telecommunications Policy Research Conference Arlie, VA - Mar. 31, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Testimony before House Public Works Comm. on Clean Water Act - Washington, DC - Apr. 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Associated Industries of NYS, Inc. Albany, NY - Apr. 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Testimony Before NYS Assem. Committee on Corps., Authorities & Comm. on PASNY Albany NY - Apr.20, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Electrification Council Conf. Cornell University, Ithaca, NY - Apr. 21, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - NBC Interview - New York City - Apr. 25-26, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - College Conference on NYS History Cultural Center, Empire Plaza Albany, NY - Apr. 30, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Meeting with NYS Utility Rate Group Albany, NY - May 3, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Testimony before Sen. Kennedy Committee Washington, DC - May 4, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - NYS Cable Television Association Albany, NY - May 9, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - NAS Committee on Gas Production Opportunities Washington, DC - May 16, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Iowa State University Rate Design Conference Ames, Iowa - May 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - House Comm. on Pub. Works & Transporatation/ Subcomm. on Investigations & Review Statement 4/19/77, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - NY State Assembly Cmte on Corp., Auths. & Comms. - Power Auth. of State of NY - Apr.20, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Statement Before Sen. Kennedy re Antitrust Enforcement - May 4, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Iowa State U. Reg. Conf. re Load Control. Res. Consery., & King Charles - May 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - National Energy Forum - May 23, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Response to AT&T Rebuttal to Testimony of NYPSC Chairman Kahn - June 1, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Energy Symposium re Energy Policy - June 11, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Hse Budget Comte Task Force on Tax Exn., Gov't Organ., & Regulation - July 14, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Transportation Association of Amer. - The Investor Panel - Sept. 16, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Hearings on International Aviation - Sept. 29, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Hse Cmte on Public Works - H.R. 8813 Federal Aviation Act of 1958 - Oct. 5, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Agency Management Seminar Charlottesville, VA - Oct. 13-15, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Brookings Policy Seminar on Regulatory Reform Oct. 18-20, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - John Hancock/GWUSeminar on Government Regulation - Oct. 21, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Aero Club Lunchon - Regulatory Reform or How Do We Get from Here to There - Oct. 25, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Talk by Alfred E. Kahn at Northwestern University 11/6/77, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Presentation to the Commuter Airline Association of America - Nov. 15, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Testimony before the Senate Aviation Subcommittee on Int'l Aviation Negs - Nov. 29, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Society of Government Economists - 12/14/77, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Brookings Seminar - Dec. 14, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - FTC - Solar Energy Symposium Washington, DC - Dec. 15-16, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc (NBER Conf. on Public Regulation) - Dec. 15-17, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - American Enterprise Institute Conference - Dec. 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Fortnightly Manuscript - Can an Economist Find Happiness Setting Public… - Jan., 1978, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Talk to the N.Y. Security Analysts New York - Feb. 2, 1978, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - McNeil-Lehrer Interview 1/10/78, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - National Energy Forum Washington, DC - Feb. 8, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University - Community Symposium - Feb. 11, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Conference for Journalists Washington, DC - Feb. 13-16, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - WAL Coporate Management Conference Miami, FL - Feb. 15-17, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - AEI Conference on Intermodal Transformation DC - Feb. 23, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Talk to the Baghot Fellows New York City - Feb. 24, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Testimony - House Subcmte on Appropriations - Feb. 28, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Senate Subcmte on Approporiations - March 2, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Testimony to Aviation Subcmte House Public Works - March 6, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - FAA Conference - Mar. 22, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Georgetown Univeristy Speech "Int'l Aviation Policy" Washington, DC - May 4, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - "The Evolving US Int'l Aviation Policy", 1978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Speech to Amer. Assoc. of Airport Execs. Cincinnati - May 22, 1978, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Deregulation of Air Transportation - Getting From Here to There Regulating Business (Article), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Remarks in Paterson, NJ 6/6/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Remarks at Cornell Alumni Reunion 6/8/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Address to Food Editor's Conference 6/11/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Speech - EEI 6/13/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Speech - Michigan State University (Gov's Conf.) 6/19/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Remarks at the Coin Teach-in 6/27/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - TV Guide Article, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Testimony on Commerce, Consumer & Monetary Affairs 6/28/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Testimony - Before Sen. Comm. On Comm., Sci,&Trans. 6/29/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - ASPEN Energy Workshop - July 13, 1979, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - JEC Testimony 7/24/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Washiongton Post Editorial Luncheon 7/31/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Food Retailers Meeting 8/13/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Speech to American Bar Assoc. in Dallas 8/15/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Speech - Food Processors & Equip. Manu. 9/11/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Talk to Florida Politicos 9/14/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Speech - National Business League in New Orleans 9/25/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Remarks to New York State Telephone ASSN. 9/26/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Remarks at Y Group Dinner 10/3/79, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Health Care-Professional Ethics, Govt. Regulation or Markets? AEI - 9/25/1980, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - The Standard Speech Johns Hopkins, Yeshiva, Bradenton, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Macalester College Speech - Nov. 12, 1980, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Chicago Health Care Speech - Nov. 20, 1980, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Can Liberalism Survive Inflation Article - Dec., 1980, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Bradenton, Fla. Manatee C. of C. - Jan. 21, 1981, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Avoiding and Economic Dunkirk: The Search for a Republican Consensus - Jan. 26, 1981, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Democratic Leadership Conference 1/31/81, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Article: Advising the President on Inflation - a Preliminary Toting-up - Feb., 1981, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Speech: American Society of Public Administration 2/5/81, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - University of New Mexico 2/11/81, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Testimony Before the Health Subcomm. of the Senate 3/13/79, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Remarks At the Economic Club of Chicago 3/13/79, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - National Newspapers Assoc. 3/16/79, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Remarks Before Nat'l Air Pollution Control Assoc. 3/21/79, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)